{
    "id": "ba4f97d8de3941539afd57a8f60302cc",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Do not spend too much money ........................ personal care products.",
            "description": "Spend + on",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "As she narrated her story, her mother's eyes filled ............................ tears.",
            "description": "Fill + with",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She often complains ............................... her nosy neighbours.",
            "description": "Complain + about",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "with",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired ............................... listening to your advice.",
            "description": "Tired + of",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When she smiled .......................... me I became very happy.",
            "description": "Smile + at",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They accused me ............................ gross negligence.",
            "description": "Accuse + of",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have benefitted immensely .............................. her help.",
            "description": "Benefit + from",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The person who broke ............................. my house was a decent guy. He only stole my food.",
            "description": "To break into is to enter forcibly. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The coach is confident that he has prepared the players ............................. the match.",
            "description": "Prepare + for",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She quit her job to devote more time .............................. her family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Why don't you ever listen .............................. me?",
            "description": "Listen + to",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sorry. I forgot .............................. your anniversary.",
            "description": "Forget + about",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "about",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}